Jefferson has organized lots of events,
including the Oil Rig Field Trip,
where the Engineering Academy was able
to go to an Oil Rig, and then spend time at the beach.
and the Amazon Warehouse Field Trip.
When I was President (2018-2019),
he was the Director of Activities.
Through fun events like our field trips, and the Rockets Social,
the Rockets Social
just beautifully executed
I can really say that joining the Academy was one of
the best decisions I’ve made in high school,
and Jefferson was a big part of that.
He’s helped plan the Airplane Student Body Meeting.
Most of my favorite moments at the
Elkins Engineering Academy are because of his leadership.
Jefferson is the type of person who
gets the job done no matter what.
He’s extremely responsible,
a determined, hard-working guy.
He’s always been dedicated
and strives to put his best foot forward.
He’s helped out every single club he’s been in.
I honestly can’t think of anyone more qualified than he is.
He’s very proactive, and he’s not afraid to take the lead.
And he has a track record of excellence in organizing events
that you want and you care about.
He’s also very focused and organized.
Jefferson has been one of the most helpful, productive,
and capable people I’ve ever met in my life.
He cares about how the members feel.
Everything he does is centered around you.
The internships that we had, the socials that we had,
it was initiated because the students wanted it.
Jefferson is a great friend
and an inspiring figure to have in your life.
He’s honestly just a chill person.
Jefferson is the best pick for Engineering Academy President.
It’s that simple!
Vote for Jefferson, 2020.
Vote for him.
Vote for Jefferson.
You should vote for Jefferson,
and I’m going to be too.
We hope to see him as the
2020-2021 Academy President!